the bear and the bee.
A version of the tale by thefablecoverage.com.
Everybody knows that bears love honey.
One day, Mr. Bear looks in his cupboard
and he can't find any honey.
Oh no, no honey.
He says so he goes into the forest to find some.
He sees a bee hive in a tree.
He smells the honey.
A honey.
He sticks his paw into the bee hive and...
A bee flies out.
Hey Bear, go away!
Says the bee.
This is not your honey.
Mr. Bear is annoyed.
I am bigger than you.
He says,
and I am stronger than you too.
I can do what I want.
No buzz off.
Mr. Bear sticks his paw into the bee hive again.
And...
That's the thing.
The bee stings him right on his nose.
I know, I know, so I'm so angry.
Grows, Mr. Bear.
He finds a big stick.
He tries to hit the bee.
He swings and he swings.
But the bee is too fast.
Mr. Bear gets angrier and angrier.
I will squash you.
Come here.
Be flies back into the bee hive.
Oh, no, you're tripped.
The old Mr. Bear.
He swings his stick at the bee hive.
Nash, smash, smash.
He smashes it to pieces and he hears a strange sound.
It gets louder and louder.
Thousands of bees fly out of the smashed bee hive.
They fly around Mr. Bear's head.
They sting him on his ear.
They sting him on his elbow.
They chase Mr. Bear through the forest.
They sting him on his arms.
His legs, his hands, and especially on his nose.
Mr. Bear runs all the way home and slams the door shut.
Bam, then he hears a voice behind him.
It's Mrs. Bear.
You did it again, didn't you?
She says.
You lost your temper.
Yes.
He says, as he cries and counts his bee stings.
Here's the bee sting medicine.
Sess Mrs. Bear.
Also, we have honey in the cupboard.
It's behind the flower.
Moral.
A hot temper always gets you into trouble.