TENGYAH!
추워는 난 남김
난 남김
Game start
아파트 아파트
어, 어, 어, 어
Kissy face, kissy face
sensey gone but
I'm trying kiss your lips for real
어, 어, 어, 어
Red hot, it's red hot
That's what I'm on
Yeah, come get me something I can feel
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
It's on too one, me like a one
You may be a ton, you may be a ton
You may be a ton now
See tomorrow but tonight go crazy
All you guys do is just me
Me, yeah, the 아파트 아파트
아파트 아파트 아파트
어, 어, 어, 어, 어
Kissy face, but, I'm trying kiss your lips for real
아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아
I'm talking drink this smoke
Sweet, I'm a night
I'm going back, I'm going back to what's up
oh, oh, oh, oh
It's on too one, me like a one
You may be a ton, you may be a ton
You may be a ton now
See tomorrow but tonight go crazy
All you guys do is just me, me, yeah
아파트 아파트 아파트
아파트 아파트
아파트 아파트 아파트 아파트
아파트 아파트 아파트
스며리로 되게
Are you ready?
빼먹은게
Get you get you hold on
I'm on my way
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Hold on hold on
I'm on my way
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Don't you want me like I want you baby
Don't you need me like I need you now
Sleep tomorrow, got to night go crazy
All you gotta do is just me, be at the end
Let's do it now
But let's do it now
If you have the pleasure, you're leaving
Mom, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I've got enough time. Move it to the hit
I've got enough time. Break it up. Break it up, tilt hit
I've got enough time. Break it up, tilt hit
I've got enough time. Break it up, tilt it up
Break it up, tilt go back
Just me, be at the end
I've got enough time,
Turn around and go to the right